Dmitrii Lisin

mrlisdim@gmail.com 8 (999) 529-5331

Since childhood, I've been in love with programming. When I began my career as an intern at an electronics design firm, I discovered that I enjoyed creating something that worked in real life rather than just inside my computer. I have finished a lot of embedded projects from different spheres and dealt with numerous instruments, protocols, and peripherals. It has always been my intention to write only high-quality, human-readable code. Had prior team leadership experience, but preferred to work as an equal member of the team. In my free time, I also prefer to extend my knowledge of programming languages, techniques, and trends by working with hobby projects.

Twitter mrlisdim Github mrdimfox Telegram @mrlisdim LinkedIn dmitrii-lisin

SKILLS

EMBEDDED DEVELOPMENT	C/C++, Zephyr, FreeRTOS, STM32, Nordic, Real-time protocols, Industrial protocols, Stack only programming
PYTHON DEVELOPMENT	FastAPI, Pydantic, ORM, WAMP protocol, Async, Threading
CI/CD	Docker, Docker Compose, Github Actions, Gitlab Pipelines
WEB DEVELOPMENT	HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, React, Parcel, Rollup
RUST	Tauri
COMMON	VSC, Gitlab, Github, Reviewing, Linux, Reading schematics, Datasheet exploring

EXPERIENCE

Team leader Jan 2020 - Present

Developed a flexible testing system for embedded electronics based on distributed micro-services connected by PubSub/RPC Web-protocol.

- Robster: flexible testing system for electronic devices (Python, WAMP, Microservice, Docker, PostgreSQL)
- Gate valve controller (ARM, STM32, Zephyr, Modbus)
- GPS tracker for a professional training (ARM, Nordic, GPS, UBlox, Ant)

Embedded Software Developer Jan 2013 - Jan 2020

Have been finished more than 20 commercial projects in embedded area including IoT, safety systems, shipbuilding.

- Pastilda: hardware password manager (STM32, ARM, Crypto Peripheral, SDIO, FatFS, FreeRTOS)
- Ship ruder control system (ARM, STM32, USB HID, FreeRTOS)
- Fire alarm system (ARM, STM32)
- MTUTA: Telemetry of vending machines (ARM, FreeRTOS, USB, SD, SIMCom, GSM, Ethernet, FTP)

EDUCATION

ITMO University

Jan 2016 - Jan 2018

Master - Intelligent Technologies in Robotics

ITMO University

Jan 2012 - Jan 2016

Bachelor - Intelligent Technologies in Robotics

LANGUAGES

English *Fluent*

INTERESTS	
Games	
Books	
Traveling	

Russian

Native Speaker

Hobby programming